<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Muse App</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="status">Connection Status:</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="init_val">0.0</string>
    <string name="eeg">EEG data:</string>
    <string name="accel">Accelerometer Data:</string>
    <string name="version">Version:</string>
    <string name="undefined">unknown</string>
    <string name="artifacts">Blinks, Jaw: </string>
    <string name="msg_count">Msg number, size: </string>
    <string name="pause">Pause/Resume</string>
    <string name="drop">Drop</string>
    <string name="muse_elem">Alpha relative:</string>
  <string name="muse_beta">Beta relative:</string>
  <string name="start">Start</string>
  <string name="timer">Timer</string>
  <string name="settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="about">About</string>
  <string name="viewdata">View Muse Connection Data</string>
  <string name="about_the_app">This android application for the Muse Headband was created with the intention of improving concentration.

    \n\nHowever, unlike the original Muse application (developed by Interaxon),
    this application will be utlizing brain wave activity in a slightly different way.
    \n\nStudies have shown that
    tasks requiring intense, directed focus (reading, studying, etc...) require different brain wave distribution when compared with meditation or sleep, for example.

    \n\nMore specifically, these focus-driven tasks require a combination of low alpha-wave activity, and high beta-wave activity.

    \n\nAfter a quick test to establish baseline brainwave levels, the user will be alerted when alpha or beta wave activity rises too high or falls too low during their task.

    \n\nThis 3rd party application was developed by Zachary Michael McGinnis, 2016
    \n\nThe Muse headband and Muse meditation application are property of InteraXon Labs.

  </string>

    <string name="permission_dialog_title">Muse Needs Your Permission</string>
    <string name="permission_dialog_description">Muse needs a few permissions to work properly. On the next screens, tap "Allow" to proceed. If you deny, Muse will not work properly until you go into your Android settings and allow.</string>
    <string name="permission_dialog_understand">I Understand</string>
</resources>
